let questions= [
    {
        question:"What is 8th wonder of the wold?",
        options:[
            "Machu Picchu",
            "Taj Mahal",
            "Petra",
            "Sigiriya"
        ],
        answer:"Sigiriya"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the highest Waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Diyaluma Ella",
            "Babarakanda Ella",
            "Duwili Ella",
            "Rawana Ella"
        ],
        answer:"Babarakanda Ella"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the capital of Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Galle",
            "Matara",
            "Kandy",
            "Colombo"
        ],
        answer:"Colombo"
    },
    {
        question:"What currency is used in Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "USD",
            "LKR",
            "INR",
            "EUR"
        ],
        answer:"LKR"
    },
    {
        question:"Which is the highest railway station in SriLanka?",
        options:[            
            "Galle",
            "Ella",
            "Pattipola",
            "Colombo Fort"
        ],
        answer:"Pattipola"
    },
    {
        question:"Which is most famous beach in Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            
            "Benthota",
            "Mirissa",
            "Unawatuna",
            "Dikwella"
        ],
        answer:"Mirissa"
    },
    {
        question:"Which is the natural harbour in Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Galle",
            "Colombo",
            "Hambanthota",
            "Trincomalee"
        ],
        answer:"Trincomalee"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the national dish of Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Kottu",
            "Fried Rice",
            "Rice and curry",
            "String hoppers"
        ],
        answer:"Rice and curry"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the highest Mountain in Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Samanala",
            "Gongala",
            "Piduruthalaga",
            "kirigalpotha"
        ],
        answer:"Piduruthalaga"
    },
    {
        question:"Which Ocean surround Sri Lanka?",
        options:[
            "Arctic Ocean",
            "Atlantic Ocean",
            "Antartic Ocean",
            "Indian Ocean"
        ],
        answer:"Indian Ocean"
    }
]